Contact

jeksogsa@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/eslam-ahmedabd-elwahed (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Laravel

Deep Learning

Computer Vision

Languages

English

Certifications

Deep Learning Specialization
Python for Everybody Specialization
Deep Learning Nanodegree

Eslam Ahmed

Technical Lead at Epsilon Al Institute Egypt

Summary

To give you a brief overview of my skill set, I have a solid understanding of computer science.

Worked in Back end Development for 8 years and working on Al field for 3 years.

Have great knowledge working with Open-CV, Deep Learning including tasks like classification /

Object detection / Segmentation / Generative models / Style Transfer and Face Detection.

Also know a lot about Machine Learning, also I know a little about Speech processing.

I am a fast, flexible code agnostic and hard worker learner.

Experience

Epsilon Al Institute

1 year 10 months

Technical Lead

January 2021 - Present (1 year)

Cairo, Egypt

Data Science and Computer Vision Instructor March 2020 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Cairo, Egypt

My Course Materials:

https://github.com/Jekso/Singularity-Data-Science

https://github.com/Jekso/Singularity-Computer-Vision

National Telecommunications Regulatory Authority (NTRA) of Egypt Software Engineer (EG-CERT)

April 2020 - January 2021 (10 months)

SiliconArena

Co-Founder

January 2018 - January 2020 (2 years 1 month)

Page 1 of 2

Bubble

Co-Founder & Senior Developer February 2016 - April 2017 (1 year 3 months)

Bubble is a Startup that made Educational Software Solutions using modern technologies like Augmented Reality , Virtual Reality , etc..

ElRoof.IO Senior PHP Developer February 2015 - February 2016 (1 year 1 month) Eldokki , Giza

Google Student Ambassador Multimedia Head February 2012 - May 2014 (2 years 4 months) Manages The Media Work Between the team

Robotics Student Organisation
Advertising Member
October 2012 - April 2014 (1 year 7 months)
Help The advertising team to make Media work

Matoreed E-Commercial Website
Co-Founder
May 2013 - December 2013 (8 months)
The CTO and The Developer of the website

Education

Free Code Camp

Full Stack Web Development Certification, Computer Software

Engineering · (2016 - 2017)

Faculty of Engineering Helwan University

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Engineering · (2011 - 2017)